In this show, members challenge
airplanes to do anything
Let's raise your personal biometric by
doing that!
I will visit you
Look at me, I have my hair untied
I will hug you tight
Yeah!
Jyousho TV with a throbbing paramedic!
So, it's started!
This time, we will send it with Kaname,
Kintoka and Aki-chan!
I'm looking forward to seeing what we
have.
I'm sure everyone is curious about
this.
I wonder what it's like.
We are excited, too.
We haven't seen it yet.
It will be released on June 23rd.
22th!
Our mini album, Heart Get, will be
released on June 22nd.
How was it?
The limited edition of FANCLUB is
completed.
We will open it now!
I'm so excited!
There are many things inside.
Wow!
We got it!
Ta-da!
It's started!
Heart-shaped!
This jacket is also released.
Look at this thickness!
This thickness!
3cm? 2cm?
Wow! 2cm!
And the back!
Look at the back!
Wow! It's beautiful!
Wow!
It's really good!
Then, let's go!
3, 2, 1, bye!
It's sugoi-kiri
It's kiriboribori
Oh ouch!
It's so good!
Can I open it?
This is the song that is included in
the album.
And this is the CD.
XX
It's all written here.
It's cute.
I'm not good at this.
Everyone's face is...
It's cute.
Let's listen to the second track.
I'm not good at this.
It's here.
Which one do you want to see first?
Let's see this one first.
CD.
We can see it together.
Cute.
BABU.
It's new.
It's coming.
It's so cute!
It's a work of art.
Look at this!
It's amazing.
It's not artistic.
Let's open it.
It's amazing.
It's so cute!
Which one should we look at first?
Wait, it's here!
There's only one.
All the types are different.
23 types.
The one I got this time is...
This one!
Look forward to this one!
There's a glitter one too.
A special glitter card.
There's a rare card.
It's so cute.
This is a paper.
You can apply for a limited event by
drawing lots.
You can apply with this.
It's like this.
It's floating.
There are many lyrics.
It's a silver color.
It's true.
It's cute.
It's floating.
Next is a CD.
It's a color of Gakusha Pair.
It's true.
It's red and green.
It's a line.
It's cute.
It's a blue-blue color.
The material is...
This is blue-blue.
This is a CD.
Sometimes I listen to Christmas Party.
I like this song.
Live and making.
Making is already released, but there
is a live version that has not been
released yet.
It is a limited edition.
I'm looking forward to it.
There are a lot of things.
This is a music video.
And a new song, Memories, is included
in the press camera when Haru first
released it.
There are a lot of things.
The making of the music video is also
included in this.
I'm excited when I see something big.
It's like a treasure box.
It's a limited edition.
I want you to take it.
It's a cover.
It's transparent.
It's shining.
It's beautiful.
Everyone's cuteness is very noticeable.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm excited.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Ah!
Ready, go!
Ah! Kana-P!
Kana-P and...
Cute!
This hair is so funny.
The wind was strong.
I was like that too.
But it's cute.
It's like this hair.
I can't show this.
No, you can't.
I can't.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's cute.
I'm so happy.
I want to be with you.
That's great.
I want to be healthy.
I got it.
I want to be with you.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Nice.
Hiyori is here.
Cute.
This pair looks fun.
I feel like I'm taking a walk.
Hiyori is cute.
Her hair is like a bear.
I think Mine is a little different.
This is a fun place.
Mine is making a fuss.
Cute.
It's like a hamster.
I don't like hamsters.
Isn't it great?
I want this data.
I want it too.
I want to do something.
I want everyone to do it.
It's a military band.
It's exciting.
It's used.
They are talking on the phone.
What are they thinking?
They are funny.
What kind of attitude?
New attitude.
It's like a vinegar.
It's Katakana.
Cute.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I don't know.
I'm in trouble.
You asked me a lot of questions.
I answered them.
I don't know the answer.
Everyone is bowing.
It's funny.
Aki-chan?
It's deep.
I'm not good at hair.
I'm getting a headache.
I got it.
We did our best.
We took a video in a certain place.
We don't want to fall.
We shouldn't fall.
It's cold when we fall.
And...
There are creatures.
There are creatures around the second
floor.
We were scared.
We were told that it's not winter.
We were surprised.
There are many creatures.
It's like a woman in the sun.
It looks fun.
It's like a place that makes me feel
youth.
Youth culture.
It's here.
There was an incident.
Someone...
It's beautiful.
Please look forward to it.
It's a memory.
This is it.
I'm going to have a hard time with
this.
To be continued.
Ah!
Eek!
Oh, I sang it.
Oh, it's a beep.
There are also photos on the card with
the lyrics.
There are a lot of them.
There's also a KUONSEN.
We took a picture of it.
It was fun.
We talked about what we liked.
We talked about how cute it was.
It was a little embarrassing.
It was a new experience.
So, I think the fans want to see the
live performance as usual.
I want to see it in person and then
I'll calm down.
I want to see it all day long.
It might be a good idea to make a day
to see this.
That's right.
We used to see this before we went to
work or school.
That's right.
It's fun.
We'll be excited.
I'll go.
We're really excited.
This is a limited edition fan club.
You can still make a reservation.
If you're curious about this video,
please check it out.
Thank you.
If you're interested in this video,
please click the good button and
subscribe to our channel.
Please.
We're waiting for your comments.
We have three days left until we go to
Yokohama Budokan.
That's great.
You're amazing.
We have three days left until we go to
Yokohama Budokan.
We'll see you there.
That's right.
We've already finished rehearsing.
It's really good.
The performance was great.
The costumes were really cute.
I think you'll like us more.
We'll do our best to make it a fun
live.
Please look forward to it.
See you in three days.
See you.
I'm going to go at full speed without
braking.
Please follow me.
Sciss, sciss, sciss, scissimoon
Sciss screamed
If I could just be there for you
This speed figure
Unend, my love, my soul
I salute you
Circular year
Enjoy everything
You've got
Forever, never ever
Need a fluster
Ready, Go
Let's free ourselves
You're a love, too, right?
Love, love!
If you think this video is fun, please
subscribe and like!
Please leave a comment!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I always say that twice.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!
I wonder why, when I smile, it's as if
the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and feel
better
If I don't, I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if it's cold and wet somewhere
again
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
There's still a view I don't know in
front of me
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I draw fragments of the future
Blank line
Now I can say it, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress